bizpr.ca 2015-05-16

# Privacy - BizPR.ca

 BizPR provide this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information received from users of this website, located at BizPR (“Site” or “Service”).This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason; each version will apply to information collected while it was in place. We will notify you of any material changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy on our Site. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.

BizPR  is a newswire service which distributes press releases on behalf of our users. If you submit a press release for distribution through our system, we will transmit your entire press release including any personal information therein contained to our media contacts and online distribution points including search engines.

By using our Site you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. “Processing” means using cookies on a computer or using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information, all of which activities will take place in the Canada. If you reside outside the Canada your personally identifiable information will be transferred to the Canada, and processed and stored there under Canada privacy standards. By visiting our Site and providing information to us, you consent to such transfer to, and processing in, the Canada.

## Summary

BizPR takes your privacy seriously and bears responsibility for protecting the data that you provide us in the normal [course](http://www.bizpr.ca/2015/04/03/course/) of interacting with our site. In order to maintain the confidentiality of all information you provide to us we strictly adhere to the following Privacy Policy outlined below.

BIZPR has in place what we believe to be appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Credit card information provided to BizPR Shop is protected against unauthorized use by 256-bit encryption and Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) security features, which scramble your personal information so that only your browser and BizPR Shop’s server can decipher it. However, no Internet, e-mail or mobile transmission is ever fully secure or error free. Because most e-mail and mobile transmissions are not encrypted, you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail, SMS or text message, or other mobile transmission.

Under 13: You must be at least 13 years old in order to register for e-mail newsletters or other features of BizPR [Services](http://www.bizpr.ca/services/). If you are under 13 years of age, please do not send any information about yourself, including your name, address or e-mail address. If we discover that we have collected any personally-identifying information from a child under the age of 13, we will remove that information from our database as soon as possible.

13-18: You must be at least 18 years old in order to Submit any User Materials on or through BizPR Services, create a profile in BizPR Community, participate in any online contests, or place an order on BizPR Shop. Visitors between the ages of 13 and 18 must obtain permission from their parents or guardians before registering for e-mail newsletters or other features of BizPR Services (excluding BizPR Community, for which they cannot register) or otherwise sending any personally-identifying information.

We do not share user information with any third parties other than via press release distribution as described above.

Our primary goals in collecting personally identifiable information are to provide you with the product and services made available through the Site, including, but not limited, to the Service, to communicate with you, and to manage your registered user account, if you have one.

**Information Collected Upon Registration**.

If you desire to have access to certain restricted sections of the Site, you will be required to become a registered user, and to submit certain personally identifiable information to BizPR. This happens in a number of instances, such as when you sign up for the Service, or if you desire to receive marketing materials and information. Personally identifiable information that we may collect in such instances may include your IP address, full user name, password, email address, city, time zone, telephone number, and other information that you decide to provide us with.

In addition, we may use your contact information to market to you, and provide you with information about, our products and services, including but not limited to our Service. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such information or communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications.

When you visit the Site, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (“Log Data” ). This Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting, the web-pages you visit, the search terms you use, and any advertisements on which you click. For most users accessing the Internet from an Internet service provider the IP address will be different every time you log on. We use Log Data to monitor the use of the Site and of our Service, and for the Site’s technical administration. We do not associate your IP address with any other personally identifiable information to identify you personally, except in case of violation of the Terms of Service.

·           A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive.

·            Cookies are required to use BizPR service.

·           We use cookies to record current session information, but do not use permanent cookies. You are required to log-in to the Site after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally accessing your account contents.

Please Contact Us to a) correct or update any personal information in BizPR database that you state is erroneous, b) opt-out of future communications from BIZPR, or c) request BIZPR to make reasonable efforts to remove your personal information from BIZPR’s database, thereby canceling your BIZPR Community profile, BIZPR newsletter registration and other BIZPR registrations. This will not necessarily remove previous public comments and other User Materials Submitted for public display on BizPR Services. The user understands that it may be impossible to delete personal information entirely because of backups and records of deletions.

BIZPR reserves the right to change this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted to this page as soon as reasonably possible, so please check this page periodically. Use of BizPR Services constitutes consent to any policy then in effect. Please make sure that you read BIZPR’s Terms of Use to understand additional terms and conditions which apply to the use of BizPR Services.

It is important to note that BizPR Services contain links to other sites, applications and services maintained by third parties that may not follow the same privacy policies as BizPR Services. For instance, clicking or tapping on a sponsorship notice or some third party logos on BizPR Services will take you to an entirely different site, application or service. These sites, applications and services may use cookies, collect data, and use the data in ways that BizPR Services would not. BIZPR is not responsible for the privacy practices or any information or materials on these other sites. Please visit these sites if you wish to review their privacy policies.

In some cases, BizPR Services may include certain embedded tools provided and controlled by third parties and governed by the terms and policies of the third parties. You should only use these third party tools if you agree to their respective terms and policies.

BizPR Services include a tool that allows you to sign in using information from your account with a third party service, such as Facebook, Twitter, Google, Yahoo, OpenID, or LinkedIn. Please be aware that those third party services are unrelated to BIZPR, and that your use of the third party services is subject to the terms and policies of those services.

For international users, please note that it may be necessary to transfer your information internationally and, in particular, your information may be transferred to and processed in the United States. For residents of the European Union: the data protection and other laws of other countries outside of the European Union may not be as comprehensive as those of the European Union. Please be assured that we take steps to ensure that your privacy is protected as described in this policy. By using this site, you agree to have your information used and transferred to the United States as set forth in this policy.

If you have any questions or comments concerning our Privacy Policy, please Contact Us or email us at bizpressrelease@gmail.com

a.We’ll never share or sell your email address to a third party Uses;

b.We may send you the free email updates you prefer;

Free email updates:

Journal and Blog. Any good press release has the chance to be selected in Journal. There are kinds of SEO tips, press release marketing tricks and other free resources for FPR registrants in Blog. (Deliver about once a month, if you agree.)

c.System updates. This item includes action required to activate membership, your press release stats, release & update notification etc. (Irregular delivery, if it is necessary.)

d.Unsubscribe.

Links

These editorial policies are created to help you understand what we accept and don’t accept for inclusion in your article contents. We would appreciate if you would please read this page first before you submit to our site.

**To Be Qualified for Our Site, Your Press release:**

a. MUST HAVE proper English, spelling, grammar, punctuation, capitalization and sentence structure. We suggest you use the which can make yours look more professional and orderly.

b. MUST NOT contain: pornography/adult material, including: contents, pictures, and keywords etc.

c. MUST NOT contain information on: hate or violence-oriented, suggest racial intolerance, advocate against any individual or group, have insulting, obscene, degrading tone, or contain profanity.

d. MUST NOT contain: Hacking/cracking content, bomb creation, support for terrorism/ radicalism/ religious fanaticism, illicit drugs or drug paraphernalia, steroid use or advocacy, weapon/ firearms/ ammunition/ balisongs/ butterfly knives or brass knuckles, or the promotion of hard alcohol/tobacco-related products or prescription drugs.

e. MUST NOT contain: the violation of any law, be considered defamatory, libelous, or infringes on the legal rights of others.

f. MUST HAVE useful information but not just piling up excessive keywords.

g. MUST BE a press release but not an attempt to slander a business.

h. MUST BE a press release but not an ad that advocates your business with boasted words.

The above provisions also apply to the followings:

**Press release[TITLE](http://www.bizpr.ca/2015/04/02/title/):**

a. Your TITLE MUST Be in upper and lower case letters with the first letter of each major word capitalized. We will not accept your TITLE in all CAPS.

b. We do not accept One Word as the press release TITLE, a MINIMUM of two unique words is required. Don’t exceed 200 words.

c. We do not accept press release TITLE that use slang terms or profanity.

d. We do not allow Prescription Drug names in the TITLE of your press release.

e. Your TITLE MUST NOT be keyword stuffed (too many redundant keywords used over and over again), but rather should read as a natural language. Don’t over-optimize your TITLE. Choose the first 3 to 5 words wisely, please.

**SUMMARY:**

a. Every press release must have a 3 to 7 sentence press release SUMMARY and not exceed 300 words. If you don’t know what to put in your SUMMARY, just use the first paragraph of your press release.

b. We do not allow HTML tags of any kind in your press release SUMMARY.

c. We do not allow blatant self-promotion in your press release SUMMARY.

d. We do not allow AUTHOR NAME in your press release SUMMARY.

e. We do not allow any website URL or Email Address in your press release SUMMARY

**Press release BODY:**

a. MUST BE a minimum of 999 words. For us, an ideal press release size is within 1999 words.

b. Please do not repeat your TITLE and AUTHOR NAME at the top of the press release BODY.

c. MUST NOT be repeated or single alphabet and sentence stuffed.

d. We will not accept press releases that are not single spaced, that do not use paragraphs to appropriately break up the body text, or that provide bulleted or numbered lists that are not formatted correctly.

e. We do not accept press releases that have extremely the same topic body and active link more than once. Don’t submit duplicate press release.

f. For customized press release, we will not accept press releases with links (in the press release body or resource box) to adult-oriented websites, including but not limited to websites that include pornography, adult-oriented sexual content.

**KEYWORDS:**

a. Please make sure you put a comma between each KEYWORD.

b. You should have a minimum of 3 to 5 KEYWORDS and a maximum of 99 words.

c. We do not accept KEYWORDS that are completely unrelated to the content of your press release.

If you have any questions or comments concerning our Editorial or Email or Privacy Policy, please Contact Us or email us at bizpressrelease@gmail.com
